

SOFTWARE ENGINEER · BIOINFORMATICS

2225 Lamley St, Baltimore, MD, 21231

□ (520)331-8386 | **S**ajstangl@gmail.com | **Q** AJStangl

Summary_

Bioinformatics Software Engineer with 3+ with years experience developing NGS analytical pipelines to identify genomic variants. Lead the development of two analytical pipeline for use by pharmaceutical partners in under one year. Highly proficient in multiple compiled and interpreted languages, work flow management systems, and formal design processes.

Experience

Personal Genome Diagnostics

Baltimore, MD

BIOINFORMATICS SOFTWARE ENGINEER, I

Oct. 2017 - PRESENT

- TODO
- TODO
- TODO

Personal Genome Diagnostics BIOINFORMATICS ASSOCIATE ENGINEER

Baltimore, MD

Feb. 2016 - Oct. 2017

- TODO
- TODO
- TODO

University of Arizona

Tucson, Arizona

Feb. 2015 - Jan 2016

- GRADUATE INTERN COMPARATIVE GENOMICS LAB
 TODO
- TODO
- TODO

Skills_

Programming Languages **Bioinformatics** Tools

Frameworks and Tools Waterfall, Agile/Scrum, Iterative, JIRA, Confluence, Sharepoint, Smartsheets

Education

University of Arizona Tucson, AZ

PROFESSIONAL SCIENCE MASTERS IN APPLIED BIOSCIENCES

May. 2016

• Focus in Bioinformatics, Data and Genomic Analysis, and Scientific Computing

University of Arizona Tucson, AZ

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MOLECULAR AND CELLULAR BIOLOGY

May. 2016

• Focus in Bioinformatics, Biochemistry, and Laboratory research

AUGUST 19, 2018 ALFRED J. STANGL · RÉSUMÉ 1